

EDUCATION

2016 - 2018 MBA HR SPPU, Pune

2002 - 2005B. Com.SRTMU, Nanded

LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

Marathi

Kannada

GAYATRI BIRADAR

SR. HR EXECUTIVE

ABOUT ME

Dedicated professional with 4+ years of experience in HR domain. Demonstrated commitment to providing top-quality support to the management for the growth and development of the organization.

Result oriented and performance-driven HR professional with interests in HR Operations, HR Generalist and Recruitment.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sr. HR Executive – Feb 2023 - Aug 2024
Petromech Engineers Pvt Ltd, Pune
(Volve Interlocks Manufacturer & Supplier)

- Payroll Processing
- Maintain and Update Employee Records & HR Database
- End to End Recruitment for all non-IT profiles
- Job Posting (Social Media and Job Portals)
- Managing Candidate database
- Collaborate with Colleges, Institutes & Placement Services
- HR Documentation
- Salary Negotiation
- Offer Generation & Offer Release
- Employee Background Verification
- Post Offer follow-ups
- Induction / Onboarding process & Joining formalities
- Employee Relations
- Grievance Handling
- Attendance and Leave management
- Statutory Compliance (PF, ESIC New Joiner Registration, MLWF)
- Performance Management Process
- Compensation and Benefits
- Employee Engagement Activities
- Exit formalities and Full & Final Settlement
- HR Admin Activities etc.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Gayatri Umakant Biradar DOB: 1983 May 25 Marital Status: Married

Phone

+91 87888 44748 +91 96044 01746 (Whatsapp

Email

gayatribiradar1@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/gayatri-biradar-520a4a232

Address

Hadapsar, Pune - 411 028

HR Executive – Oct 2021 - Feb 2023 Floating Minds Infotech, Pune

(Software Training Institute)

- End to End Recruitment for all profiles
- Sourcing, Screening, Mass-mailing
- Job Posting (Social Media and Job Portals)
- Managing candidate database
- Collaborate with Colleges, Institutes & Placement Services
- Induction & Joining formalities
- Employee Engagement Activities
- Admin Activities etc.

HR Recruiter to Team Leader – May 2018 - March 2020 Haze Busting Consultancy Services, Pune (Consultancy and Placement Services)

- End to End Recruitment (IT & Non-IT)
- Sourcing, Screening, Mass-mailing
- Job Posting (Social Media and Job Portals)
- Managing candidate database
- Employee Engagement Activities
- Attendance and Leave management
- Trained new joiners & supported to achieve their targets

Summer Internship – May 2017 - July 2017 Vishay Components India Pvt Ltd, Pune (Manufacturer of Semiconductors and Capacitors)

- Attendance and Leave Management
- Scheduling and arranging Preliminary interviews
- CSR
- Admin Activities

SOFTWARE SKILL

■ MS Office
■ MS Outlook

CERTIFICATION & COURSES

- HR Executive Training Course
- HR Course on Payroll and Statutory Compliances
- SAP Success Factor Employee Central (Pursuing)